Hello everyone and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
Hi everyone.
大家好。
My name is Kathryn and today Marco we're talking about money.
我是Kathryn，今天Marco，我们要聊聊钱。
That's right.
没错。
We're going to take a look at another lesson about money but this time we're going to learn
我们将再看一节关于钱的课，但这次我们要学习
a little bit more about coins in the United States.
更多关于美国硬币的知识。
That's right.
没错。
Different coins, so different sizes and shapes, they have different names because they represent
不同的硬币，大小和形状各异，它们有不同的名字，因为代表
different amounts of money.
不同的金额。
So today we're going to learn the names of those coins and we're also going to learn
所以今天我们要学习这些硬币的名字，还要了解
a little bit about British money.
一点关于英国货币的知识。
So let's check out the dialogue.
那我们来看看对话吧。
Help me organize these coins.
帮我整理这些硬币。
That's a lot of money.
这钱真多啊。
What'd you do, break the piggy bank?
你干嘛了，把存钱罐砸了？
Yeah, I'm going to go to the bank and change it for bills but first I have to separate
是啊，我打算去银行换成纸币，但得先把它们
them into little piles.
分成小堆。
Okay.
好的。
I'll find all the quarters and dimes while you sort the nickels and pennies.
你整理五分和一分硬币的时候，我来找所有两角五分和一角硬币。
Great.
太好了。
Then we can add everything up and take it to the bank.
然后我们把总数加起来，拿到银行去。
I found some coins that are not from here.
我找到了一些不是这里的硬币。
Oh yeah, those are from my trip to London.
哦，那些是我去伦敦旅行时带回来的。
I have like 90 pence but in all it won't add up to one pound.
我大概有90便士，但加起来还不到一英镑。
Are you sure the bank will change these coins for you?
你确定银行会帮你换这些硬币吗？
Hopefully.
希望吧。
All right, we're back so let's take a look at some of this language on Language Takeaway.
好了，我们回来了，现在来看看“语言要点”中的一些表达。
Language Takeaway.
语言要点。
So first up, Marco, we have this funny phrase, break the piggy bank.
首先，Marco，我们有一个有趣的短语，“break the piggy bank”。
What is a piggy bank?
什么是存钱罐？
That's right, a piggy bank.
没错，存钱罐。
Now you may have seen this, it has the shape of a little pig.
你可能见过这个，它是个小猪形状的东西。
It's usually made out of plastic or ceramic and it has a little hole at the top where
通常由塑料或陶瓷制成，顶部有个小孔，
you can put in coins and just basically save your money there.
你可以把硬币放进去，基本上就是在那里存钱。
All right, so this is a pig-shaped bank but it's a bank you keep in your room.
好的，所以这是一个猪形的存钱罐，但它是放在你房间里的存钱罐。
Mostly children have these, right?
大多数孩子都有这个，对吧？
Yeah, so if you want to save your change or you want to save some of your coins that you
是的，如果你想存零钱，或者想存一些硬币，
have or teach your children about saving money, then usually they have a little piggy bank
或者教孩子存钱，那么他们通常会有个小存钱罐
where they can store their money.
来放钱。
So when you break the piggy bank, usually these were made of ceramic.
所以当你“break the piggy bank”时，通常这些存钱罐是陶瓷做的。
So to spend the money, you have to decide when it's very, very special or important.
要花这些钱，你得在非常特别或重要的时候决定。
So you have to break the entire bank and that's when you take all the coins you've been saving.
所以你得把整个存钱罐砸开，那时你才能拿出所有存起来的硬币。
Right, exactly, because they didn't really have a little hole where you could take it
对，没错，因为它们没有小孔可以
out from.
把钱取出来。
So when you wanted to take your money out, you literally had to break it.
所以当你想拿钱时，你真的得把它砸开。
Break it, all right.
砸开它，好的。
So that's the piggy bank.
这就是存钱罐。
But what do we store inside a piggy bank?
但我们在存钱罐里放什么呢？
We don't store bills, do we?
我们不放纸币，对吧？
That's right, no, we store coins.
没错，我们放硬币。
So this is an interesting word, bill, you know, like the name Bill, Bill Clinton, for
所以这是一个有趣的词，“bill”，你知道，就像名字Bill，比如Bill Clinton。
example.
例如。
Bills are the paper money that we use.
“Bills”是我们用的纸币。
All right, but not capitalized like a name because this is a normal, a common noun.
好的，但不像名字那样大写，因为这是一个普通名词。
Bills represent all paper money.
“Bills”代表所有纸币。
So I could get, I could ask for change.
所以我可以要，我可以要求换零钱。
Could I have the change in bills, please?
能给我换成纸币吗？
That's right.
没错。
And if I'm at a store, they'll give me bills, maybe a $5 bill, $10 bill.
如果我在商店，他们会给我纸币，可能是5美元纸币、10美元纸币。
This also counts for other currencies.
这也适用于其他货币。
So if I'm in China, I might get my renminbi, my yuan in bills.
所以如果我在中国，我可能会拿到人民币、元纸币。
So it's just a general name for paper money.
所以这只是纸币的通用名称。
That's right.
没错。
So, but what we store in the piggy bank are coins.
但我们在存钱罐里放的是硬币。
Now talking specifically about the types of coins or the different amounts that these
现在具体谈谈硬币的类型或它们代表的
represent, let's take a look at those more in detail.
不同金额，让我们更详细地看看这些。
All right, so first up we've got quarters.
好的，首先我们有“quarters”。
Now this should be pretty easy if you know your time because a quarter is one-fourth
如果你知道时间，这应该很容易，因为“quarter”是某物的四分之一。
of something.
某物的四分之一。
So if we're talking about money, it's a quarter of a dollar or 25 cents.
所以如果我们在谈钱，它就是一美元的四分之一，或25美分。
That's right.
没错。
So 25 cents or a quarter of a dollar or one-fourth of a dollar, we just call it a quarter.
所以25美分，或一美元的四分之一，我们就叫它“quarter”。
So you know, most machines or pay phones, you need to insert quarters.
你知道，大多数机器或付费电话，你需要投“quarters”。
That's right.
没错。
So we recognize the quarter because it's the biggest coin and it has a big eagle on one
所以我们认出“quarter”，因为它是最的硬币，一面有只大鹰，
side and on the other side it has George Washington's head.
另一面有乔治·华盛顿的头像。
George Washington, that's right.
乔治·华盛顿，没错。
Now the next in line or the next coin that we're going to take a look at are dimes.
接下来我们要看的硬币是“dimes”。
Dimes.
“Dimes”。
Now these are also recognizable because they're the smallest coins, but that does not mean
现在这些硬币也很容易辨认，因为它们是最小的硬币，但这并不意味着
they're the smallest amount.
它们就是面额最小的。
Dimes are actually the second largest.
实际上，10美分硬币是第二大的。
They're 10 cents.
它们是10美分。
They're 10 cents or one-tenth of a dollar.
它们是10美分，或者说一美元的十分之一。
And so you can say they're 10 cents or you can say dime.
所以你可以说它们是10美分，或者直接说dime。
So do you have, I don't know, if you have 10 dimes, that means you've got a dollar.
那么，我不知道，如果你有10个dime，那就意味着一美元。
That's right.
没错。
10 dimes equal one dollar.
10个dime等于一美元。
And the face on the dime is Thomas Jefferson.
而dime上的头像，是托马斯·杰斐逊。
Alexander Hamilton.
亚历山大·汉密尔顿。
I don't know.
我不知道。
No, he was the first, well, he created basically the Department of the Treasury.
不，他是第一个，嗯，他基本上创建了财政部。
But Thomas Jefferson is on another coin and that's what we're going to look at next.
但托马斯·杰斐逊在另一种硬币上，那就是我们接下来要看的。
That's right.
没错。
The nickel.
5美分硬币。
The nickel is like the metal, you know, nickel.
5美分硬币就像金属镍一样，你知道的，镍。
And yeah, so this one is a little bit bigger than the dime, but not as big as the quarter.
是的，这个比dime大一点，但没有quarter那么大。
I think it's a little bit thicker maybe.
我觉得它可能厚一点。
It is thicker, but it's not as much money.
它更厚，但面额没那么大。
A nickel is five cents.
一个5美分硬币是5美分。
Five cents.
5美分。
So one-twentieth of a dollar.
所以是一美元的二十分之一。
That's right.
没错。
One-twentieth of a dollar.
一美元的二十分之一。
So this is what we call a nickel.
这就是我们说的nickel。
So you would call this coin, you would say, hey, do you have any nickels?
所以你会叫这种硬币，你会说，嘿，你有nickel吗？
Dimes and nickels usually go together.
Dime和nickel通常一起出现。
I don't know why.
我不知道为什么。
Nickels and dimes.
Nickels and dimes。
Nickels and dimes means he doesn't have very much money.
Nickels and dimes意味着他没多少钱。
That's right.
没错。
So, yeah, and then on this coin you have the face of Thomas Jefferson.
所以，是的，然后这种硬币上有托马斯·杰斐逊的头像。
That's right.
没错。
Okay.
好的。
And finally we have the only coin that's not silver colored.
最后，我们有唯一一种不是银色的硬币。
It's actually more of a copper color.
它实际上更接近铜色。
That would be the penny.
那就是1美分硬币。
The penny.
1美分硬币。
That's right.
没错。
One cent or one penny is the smallest of the coins.
1美分或1 penny是最小的硬币。
And actually you need 100 of these to make one dollar.
实际上，你需要100个这样的硬币才能凑成一美元。
That's right.
没错。
And it's very unique because it's a different color.
而且它很独特，因为颜色不同。
It's the smallest amount.
它是面额最小的。
And the face on this coin, do you know this one?
这种硬币上的头像，你知道是谁吗？
Yes.
知道。
This one is Abraham Lincoln.
这个是亚伯拉罕·林肯。
Correct.
正确。
All right.
好了。
So we've got all these important people.
所以我们有这么多重要人物。
All of them were presidents actually except for Alexander Hamilton.
除了亚历山大·汉密尔顿，他们其实都是总统。
That's right.
没错。
And actually I think Alexander Hamilton looks good.
实际上，我觉得亚历山大·汉密尔顿长得不错。
Better than the rest.
比其他人都好看。
I don't know why.
我不知道为什么。
He was a pretty handsome man.
他是个相当英俊的男人。
Actually, no, he was said to be very funny looking I think.
实际上，不，据说他长得挺滑稽的，我觉得。
So actually all of these coins, you can call them by these names and everyone will recognize
所以实际上所有这些硬币，你可以用这些名字称呼它们，每个人都会认出
them, especially in the US.
它们，尤其是在美国。
Now I don't really think they apply to any other country as we saw later on, for example,
现在，我不认为这些适用于其他国家，就像我们后来看到的，例如，
money in England or the United Kingdom.
英国或联合王国的货币。
But usually in the US, if you say, hey, do you have any spare change or do you have any
但在美国，通常如果你说，嘿，你有零钱吗，或者你有
nickels and dimes?
nickels和dimes吗？
Or can I borrow a penny?
或者我能借一个penny吗？
Can I borrow a penny?
我能借一个penny吗？
Usually in the US, they have these little things called take a penny, leave a penny,
通常在美国，他们有一种小东西叫“拿一个penny，留一个penny”，
right?
对吧？
Or give a penny, take a penny.
或者“给一个penny，拿一个penny”。
You see these because pennies are not worth very much money.
你会看到这些，因为penny不值多少钱。
And oftentimes people will leave a penny and if you have, it may something costs 26 cents,
而且经常人们会留下一个penny，如果你有，比如某样东西要26美分，
but you only have a quarter, you can take a penny and then spend that.
但你只有一个quarter，你可以拿一个penny然后花掉。
So they're basically free pennies you might see in a store.
所以它们基本上是在商店里可能看到的免费penny。
And then also if you get change, maybe you don't want to carry those pennies around or
然后如果你收到找零，也许你不想带着那些penny或
that change.
那些零钱到处走。
You just leave that there.
你就把它们留在那里。
And then it's kind of a way of recycling this small amount of money, which is very interesting.
然后这算是一种回收这些小面额钱币的方式，非常有趣。
It is very interesting.
确实非常有趣。
But we're going to actually take a look at some British currency.
但我们接下来要看看一些英国货币。
So let's take another listen to the dialogue.
那我们再听一遍对话。
And when we come back, we'll explore that.
等我们回来，再探讨那个问题。
Help me organize these coins.
帮我整理这些硬币。
That's a lot of money.
这钱可真不少。
What'd you do?
你做了什么？
Break the piggy bank?
把存钱罐砸了？
Yeah, I'm going to go to the bank and change it for bills.
是啊，我打算去银行换成纸币。
But first I have to separate them into little piles.
但首先我得把它们分成小堆。
Okay.
好的。
I'll find all the quarters and dimes while you sort the nickels and pennies.
你整理五分和一角硬币时，我来找所有两角五分和一角硬币。
Great.
太好了。
Then we can add everything up and take it to the bank.
然后我们可以加起来，带去银行。
I found some coins that are not from here.
我找到了一些不是这里的硬币。
Oh yeah, those are from my trip to London.
哦，对，那些是我去伦敦旅行时带的。
I have like 90 pence, but it won't add up to one pound.
我大概有90便士，但凑不到一英镑。
Are you sure the bank will change these coins for you?
你确定银行会帮你换这些硬币吗？
Hopefully.
希望如此。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So let's take a look at these British words on Language Takeaway Part 2.
那我们来看看语言小贴士第二部分的这些英式词汇。
So here we've got British currency, the pound, right, is the name of the currency.
这里我们有英国货币，英镑，对吧，是货币的名称。
So in America we have the dollar.
在美国我们用美元。
In Britain we have the pound.
在英国我们用英镑。
Is it the sterling pound?
是叫“斯特林镑”吗？
Yeah, pound sterling.
对，英镑。
The pound sterling.
英镑。
Pound sterling.
And I think that has to do with weight, I'm sure.
我觉得这跟重量有关，我敢肯定。
But here we've got it divided into small and large quantities.
但这里我们把它分成了小面额和大面额。
So where we have coins, we might have pence.
我们有硬币，可能是便士。
Sounds like cents.
听起来像美分。
Right, exactly.
对，没错。
And I think actually the penny might come from the British term pence.
而且我觉得“penny”这个词可能来自英国的“pence”。
I'm sure it does.
我肯定是的。
They're very similar and the meaning is basically one hundredth of a pound.
它们很相似，意思基本上是一英镑的百分之一。
Right, exactly.
对，没错。
And a pound is basically what you would say in the US, a dollar.
一英镑基本上就相当于你们美国说的一美元。
A pound is the currency of England.
英镑是英国的货币。
But actually, you know how in the United States people would say, you know, a hundred bucks,
但实际上，你知道在美国人们会说“一百 bucks”，
which would be a hundred dollars.
也就是一百美元。
Over there they say one hundred quid.
在那里他们就说“一百 quid”。
Quid.
奎德。
So yeah, this is actually important slang.
对，这其实是个重要的俚语。
In America I would spend five bucks at the movies.
在美国，我花五美元看电影。
In Britain I would spend five quid.
在英国，我花五奎德。
And now that's a slang term for one pound.
现在这是指一英镑的俚语。
That's right.
没错。
And actually I've heard also like 50p, which I think means 50 cents.
而且我还听过像50p，我觉得那是50美分的意思。
Yeah, pence.
对，便士。
Pence.
便士。
Yeah, so 50p.
对，所以是50p。
So you could say this stick of, or this pack of gum costs 50p.
所以你可以说这条口香糖或这包口香糖要50p。
So 50 pence.
就是50便士。
That's right.
没错。
Half of a pound.
半英镑。
So currency, obviously the currencies are different, but also it is interesting to learn
所以货币，显然货币不同，但学习当地的说法也很有趣。
the way that you would say it locally.
你在当地会怎么表达。
So you know, next time if you are in Britain or you're talking to an English person, then
所以下次如果你在英国或跟英国人聊天，如果他们提到50奎德，你就知道他们在说50英镑。
you'd know if they say, you know, 50 quid, you understand they're talking about 50 pounds.
没错。
Exactly.
完全正确。
So, but they don't use the euro over there.
不过他们那边不用欧元。
No, they don't.
不，他们不用。
Not in Great Britain.
在英国不用。
They do use the euro on the continents of France, Italy.
在法国、意大利这些欧洲大陆国家，他们确实用欧元。
And the euro is the name of that currency.
欧元就是那种货币的名称。
Okay.
好的。
All right.
明白了。
So that's good stuff.
所以这些内容不错。
And now lastly, although we saw it at the beginning of the dialogue, let's talk about
最后，虽然我们在对话开头看到过，但让我们谈谈
what this person wants to do.
这个人想做什么。
He wants to change these coins into bills.
他想把这些硬币换成纸币。
That's right.
没错。
So the verb when you need to exchange money is to change money.
所以当你需要兑换货币时，动词是“换钱”。
So let's say if I go to England and all I have is dollars, I would say I want to change
比方说，如果我去英国，只有美元，我会说我想换
money.
钱。
Okay.
好的。
You could also say exchange, but when we're speaking to one another, we normally just
你也可以说“兑换”，但当我们互相交谈时，通常只说
say change.
“换”。
Right.
对。
Because even the places are sometimes called like money changers.
因为就连那些地方有时也被称为“换钱处”。
You know, they say that or something like that.
你知道，他们就是这么说的，或者类似的话。
Exactly.
没错。
And so if I want to change money, that means I want to maybe change dollars for euros or
所以如果我想换钱，意思是我可能想把美元换成欧元，或者
dollars for pounds.
把美元换成英镑。
But this also can mean I want to change a dollar for some quarters.
但这也可以指我想把一张美元换成一些25美分硬币。
Right.
对。
Because I need quarters for like a laundry machine or a telephone.
因为我需要25美分硬币，比如用来用洗衣机或打电话。
Right.
对。
And I've heard also the term is to break.
我还听过另一个词是“break”。
So if maybe you have a $10 bill and you need maybe a $5 bill, but you don't have like,
所以如果你有一张10美元钞票，但你需要一张5美元钞票，而你没有，
you ask the person to break that money.
你就请对方帮你“break”那笔钱。
So you say, can you break this bill?
所以你会说，你能帮我破开这张钞票吗？
Yeah.
嗯。
And that actually makes sense because a bill normally you break something that's big into
这其实很合理，因为通常“break”是把大的东西弄成
smaller pieces.
更小的碎片。
So if you think about it, if I break a glass, it becomes many pieces.
所以你想一下，如果我打碎一个玻璃杯，它会变成很多碎片。
Well, if I break a $5 bill, I want maybe $1.
嗯，如果我破开一张5美元钞票，我可能想要1美元。
I get five of those.
我就能得到五张。
There's one piece and then it breaks into many pieces.
它是一整张，然后破成很多张。
So to break means to ask for smaller change.
所以“break”意思是要求换成更小的零钱。
That's right.
没错。
So maybe next time you guys need change, you can go up to someone and say, excuse me, can
所以下次你们需要零钱时，可以走到某人面前说，打扰一下，你能
you change this $5 bill for me?
帮我把这张5美元钞票换开吗？
Or can you break this $5 bill for me?
或者你能帮我把这张5美元钞票破开吗？
That's right.
没错。
All right.
好的。
So a lot of interesting language, very useful stuff.
所以有很多有趣的语言，非常实用的内容。
Let's listen to the dialogue one last time.
让我们最后再听一遍对话。
Help me organize these coins.
帮我整理这些硬币。
That's a lot of money.
这钱真不少。
What'd you do?
你做了什么？
Break the piggy bank?
打碎了存钱罐？
Yeah, I'm going to go to the bank and change it for bills.
是啊，我打算去银行换成纸币。
But first I have to separate them into little piles.
但首先我得把它们分成小堆。
Okay.
好的。
I'll find all the quarters and dimes while you sort the nickels and pennies.
我来找所有25美分和10美分硬币，你整理5美分和1美分硬币。
Great.
太好了。
Then we can add everything up and take it to the bank.
然后我们可以加起来，拿到银行去。
I found some coins that are not from here.
我发现了一些不是这里的硬币。
Oh yeah.
哦，是啊。
Those are from my trip to London.
那些是我去伦敦旅行时带的。
I have like 90 pence, but in all it won't add up to one pound.
我大概有90便士，但加起来还不到一英镑。
Are you sure the bank will change these coins for you?
你确定银行会帮你换这些硬币吗？
Hopefully.
希望吧。
All right.
好的。
Coming back to the topic now, you seem to know a lot about this stuff.
现在回到话题，你似乎对这些很了解。
Let's test your knowledge here.
我们来测试一下你的知识。
On the $100 bill, who do we find?
在100美元钞票上，我们能看到谁？
What president or one person?
哪位总统或某个人？
Benjamin Franklin.
本杰明·富兰克林。
That's right.
没错。
But he wasn't a president, right?
但他不是总统，对吧？
He was not.
他不是。
He was a very important figure in American history.
他是美国历史上非常重要的人物。
Many people are familiar with the story of Benjamin Franklin and the kite with the key
很多人都熟悉本杰明·富兰克林和风筝上挂着钥匙的故事。
on it.
So he discovered electricity.
所以他发现了电。
That's right.
没错。
He was a very important inventor and also an important person when it comes to the creation
他是一位非常重要的发明家，在创建美国方面也是重要人物。
of America.
That's right.
没错。
Now, the smaller of the bills would be the $1 bill.
现在，面额较小的纸币是1美元钞票。
And actually now you have a $1 coin as well.
实际上现在也有1美元硬币。
But on the $1 bill, do you know who's on there?
但在1美元钞票上，你知道上面是谁吗？
I think it's George Washington also, right?
我想也是乔治·华盛顿，对吧？
I think so, yeah.
我想是的，嗯。
So he's on the quarter and on the $1 bill.
所以他出现在25美分硬币和1美元钞票上。
We like to recycle our presidents.
我们喜欢重复使用我们的总统。
The $20 bill then would be Abraham Lincoln, right?
20美元钞票上应该是亚伯拉罕·林肯，对吧？
Oh, that's right.
哦，没错。
So they're actually on...
所以他们实际上在……
That's kind of unfair though.
这有点不公平。
These are favorite presidents in the United States.
这些是美国最受欢迎的总统。
But they haven't changed over time.
但他们一直没有变过。
In other countries, you see that they change according to the important person that's in
在其他国家，你会看到他们根据政府中的重要人物而改变，或者比如在中国，上面有毛主席，而以前没有。
government or maybe, for example, in China, you have Chairman Mao on there, which before
you didn't.
Or in England, you have Queen Elizabeth, before was the previous ruler, which I think was
或者在英国，上面有伊丽莎白女王，之前是前任统治者，我想是乔治六世国王。
King George VI.
But in the US, guys flat out 100 years ago, these guys haven't changed them since then.
但在美国，这些家伙一百年前就定型了，从那以后就没变过。
Well, I think what America likes to celebrate its creation.
嗯，我觉得美国喜欢庆祝它的创立。
And so...
所以...
Which is still a very young country, right?
它仍然是一个非常年轻的国家，对吧？
Right.
对。
1776, so it's only been, what, 240 years.
1776年，所以到现在才，嗯，240年。
So yeah, the idea is basically that we celebrate the founding, so the beginning of the republic.
所以是的，基本上就是庆祝建国，也就是共和国的开端。
And the men who are involved in that, they're called the founders.
而那些参与其中的人，被称为开国元勋。
George Washington, James Madison, Alexander Hamilton, all of them, Benjamin Franklin,
乔治·华盛顿、詹姆斯·麦迪逊、亚历山大·汉密尔顿，还有本杰明·富兰克林，
these people are very important in the history of America.
这些人在美国历史上非常重要。
And that's why we celebrate them on our money.
这就是为什么我们把他们的头像印在钱上。
The one exception, of course, is Abraham Lincoln.
当然，有一个例外，就是亚伯拉罕·林肯。
He was from the 1860s.
他是19世纪60年代的人。
Right, 16th president.
对，第16任总统。
That's right.
没错。
And he was very important because of the Civil War, and a lot of the changes that later happened
他非常重要，因为内战以及后来对我们宪法做出的许多修改。
to our constitution.
And so he's another person who's maybe added on.
所以他是另一个后来被加进去的人。
So he's basically the last guy you guys kind of celebrate, because you don't have, I don't
所以他基本上是你最后庆祝的人，因为你们没有，我不知道...
know...
Franklin Delano Roosevelt.
富兰克林·德拉诺·罗斯福。
Right, or Bill Clinton, or something like this.
对，或者比尔·克林顿之类的。
Not yet.
还没有。
Right, so I guess we got to wait a while.
对，所以我想我们得等一段时间。
But that's very interesting.
但这非常有趣。
This history aspect of currencies is actually very, very interesting.
货币的这个历史方面其实非常非常有意思。
It is.
是的。
And one thing I'd like to add about quarters is that in the 2000s, so from 2000, I think,
关于25美分硬币，我想补充一点，在21世纪初，大概从2000年开始，
on, the United States started to make state quarters.
美国开始发行州纪念币。
So you'll see oftentimes these quarters with a picture of a state, New Hampshire, Maryland,
所以你经常会看到这些25美分硬币上印有某个州的图案，比如新罕布什尔州、马里兰州、
Illinois, California, and a special symbol of that state.
伊利诺伊州、加利福尼亚州，以及该州的特殊标志。
And so these are special quarters from the last maybe 10 years or so.
这些是过去大概十年左右发行的特殊25美分硬币。
Yeah, I remember seeing these because usually on the other side of the quarter, on one side
是的，我记得见过这些，因为通常25美分硬币的一面是乔治·华盛顿，
you had George Washington, on the other side you had the eagle, the emblem of the flag,
另一面是鹰，我想是国旗上的标志。
I guess.
Well, not the flag, but the national bird or the republic.
嗯，不是国旗，而是国鸟或共和国的象征。
But now you have these states, and it says Delaware, and it has a little maybe, I don't
但现在这些硬币上有各州图案，写着特拉华州，可能还有一朵小花之类的代表该州的东西。
know, flower or something that's representative of these states.
So that was actually very nice.
所以那其实挺不错的。
It was a collector's type thing as well, right?
那也是一种收藏品，对吧？
People were collecting these.
人们都在收集这些。
That's right.
没错。
You can collect all 50.
你可以收集全部50个州的。
Some people did that.
有些人就这么做了。
And you still see them in use.
而且你现在还能看到它们在流通。
So those are the state quarters.
所以那些就是州纪念币。
And those generally are newer quarters.
那些通常是较新的25美分硬币。
Okay, interesting.
好的，有意思。
All right, guys.
好了，各位。
So we're out of time, but if you guys have any questions or doubts, you could find us
我们时间到了，但如果你们有任何问题或疑问，可以到EnglishPod.com找我们，
at EnglishPod.com, and we'll see you guys there.
我们会在那里见。
Bye.
再见。
Come on in, guys.
进来吧，各位。